HAYDEN MOORE

MAKER & INNOVATOR



htmoor@gmail.com



haydenmoore.nz



027 4737 218



2/24 College Rd Saint Johns, Auckland

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming

Maker

MS Excel

Designer

Electrical Engineering

Product Design

CAD

CNC

Vector Graphics

Woodwork

Metalwork

3D Printer

Laser Cutter

Automation

MS Word

OTHER SKILLS

Team Collaboration

Passionate About Making

Communicating Ideas

Teaching Concepts

EDUCATION

BSc – Computer Science

University of Auckland 2017

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a maker and innovator with two years professional experience in product design and years of personal projects. I want to gain more professional experience through innovation-based roles alongside focusing on entrepreneurship and commercialising my own projects.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGIST (November 2017 – Present)
Spire Construction R&D

- Business cases to analyse potential projects.
- Followed product design methodology to converge aesthetic and functional prototypes.
- Prototyped products using electronics, 3D design, 3D printing, firmware and software.
- Agile team environment.
- Managed various software developers.

CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST (August 2017 – November 2017)
Unleash Space (University of Auckland)

- Part of the initial team that set up the maker space and its various machines.
- Created and delivered machine training sessions and various workshops to students.
- Gave advice to students on projects, materials, techniques, business, design and idea execution.

ENTREPRENEURIAL EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT ENGINEER / CO-FOUNDER (2017 – Present)

 Shwoop is an advertising agency that creates digital engagements and meaningful connections.
 I am primarily in charge of creating hardware products that facilitate engagement.

PRODUCT ENGINEER / CO-FOUNDER (2019 – Present)

• *OHM* creates performance enhancing heat-suits for cyclists. I am primarily in charge of developing the control module and suit.

100K Challenge with Shwoop (2018)

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Numerous personal projects (ideas into products)

First aid training (2017)

Defining machine operation safety policies at Unleash (2017)